Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Committees (Box 69)
    - Degree Program Proposal Review Committee (Box 76)
      - Hazardous materials SPEA/certificate, 1985 (Box 76)
      - Psychology/BS, 1985 (Box 76)
      - Psychological education, 1985 (Box 76)
      - Biology/BA, 1986 (Box 76)
      - Liberal studies/Masters, 1986 (Box 76)
      - Instrumentation science/MS, 1986 (Box 76)
      - Computer integrated manufacturing technology, 1986 (Box 76)
      - East Asian studies/ Graduate area certificate, 1986 (Box 76)
      - Mathematics/BA, 1987 (Box 76)
    - Disaster Control Committee, 1971 (Box 76)
    - Distinguished Alumni Service Award (Committee for) (Box 76)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 76)
      - 1986 (Box 76)
    - Distinguished Professorships, 1980-1981 (Box 76)
    - Distinguished Ranks Committee (Box 76)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 76)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 76)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 76)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 76)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 76)
      - 1975-1977 (Box 76)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 76)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 76)
      - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 76)
    - Distinguished Teaching Awards (Committee on) (Box 76)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 76)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 76)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 76)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 76)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 76)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 76)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 76)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 76)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 76)
      - 1984 (Box 76)
      - 1985 (Box 76)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 76)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 76)
    - Dormitory Ad Hoc Task Force Committee (Box 76)
      - 1971-1987 (Box 76)
      - 1971 (Box 76)
    - East Asia Committee, 1974 (Box 76)
    - Economic Development (Committee for), 1977-1978 (Box 76)
    - Educational Programs of the Indianapolis and Bloomington Campuses, 1974 (Box 76)
    - Educational Opportunities for Veterans (Committee on), 1973-1974 (Box 76)
    - John Edwards Trust Fund Committee (Box 76)
      - 1984 (Box 76)
      - 1986 (Box 76)
    - Employment (Chancellor's Committee on), 1972-1973 (Box 76)
    - Endowed Chairs (Committee on), 1975-1976 (Box 76)
    - Energy (University Committee on) (Box 76)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 76)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 76)
    - Enrollment Policy Committee Report, 1979 (Box 76)
    - Environmental Health Committee, 1971 (Box 76)
    - Equality of Educational Opportunities Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 76)
    - Equipment Committee (Box 76)
      - 1971-1978 (Box 76)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 76)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 76)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
    - Faculty Advising Committee, 1971-1975 (Box 76)
    - Faculty Council (Box 76)
      - General, 1971-1975 (Box 76)
      - Constitution, 1969-1970 (Box 76)
      - Faculty Council Nominating Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 76)
      - Nominating Committee, 1970 (Box 76)
      - Election Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 76)
      - Faculty Promotion Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 76)
    - Faculty (Non-tenured) - Committee to Consider Procedures in Non reappointment, 1971-1972 (Box 76)
    - Faculty (Retiring) - Committee to Plan Dinner for, 1971 (Box 76)
    - Fee Structure (Committee on) (Box 76)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 76)
      - 1972-1973, (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 76)
    - Fee Courtesy Appeals Committee (Box 76)
      - 1982 (Box 76)
      - 1983 (Box 76)
      - 1986 (Box 76)
    - Fine Arts Advisory Committee (Box 76)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 76)
      - IUPUFW, 1979-1980 (Box 76)
    - Fiscal Policy Committee (Box 76)
      - Minutes, 1973 (Box 76)
      - 1972-1973, (2 boxes) (Box 77)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 77)
      - 1974 (Box 77)
    - Football Coach Ad Hoc Committee, 1982 (Box 77)
    - Ford Foundation Fine Arts Collection Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 77)
    - Foreign Students Advisory Committee, 1970-1979; (2 folders) (Box 77)
    - Founders Day and Homecoming Committee (Box 77)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 77)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 77)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 77)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 77)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 77)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 77)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 77)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 77)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 77)
      - 1981 (Box 77)
      - 1982 (Box 77)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 77)
      - 1986 (Box 77)
    - Foust, Cleon (Committee to Honor), 1973 (Box 77)
    - Fraternity Housing Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 77)
    - Fringe Benefits Committee (Box 77)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 77)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 77)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 77)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 77)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 77)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 77)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 77)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 77)
      - 1973-1980 (Box 77)
    - Fulbright Hays Committee (Box 77)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 77)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Futures Research and Educational Development Committee (Box 77)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 77)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 77)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 77)
      - 1981 (Box 77)
      - April 1981 (Box 77)
      - 1981 (Box 77)
      - 1982 (Box 77)
      - January 1982 (Box 77)
      - 1983 (Box 77)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 77)
      - 1986 (Box 78)
      - 1987 (Box 78)
    - Future Studies (Steering Committee for) (Box 78)
      - 1972-1975 (Box 78)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 78)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 78)
    - General and Technical Studies Advisory Committee (Box 78)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 78)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 78)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 78)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 78)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 78)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 78)
    - Halls of Residence Committee (Box 78)
      - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - Advisory search committee, 1972; emph: (RESTRICTED) (Box 78)
      - 1972-1973, (3 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1970-1974 (Box 78)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 78)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 78)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 78)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 78)
    - Heraldic Banners Committee (Box 78)
      - 1972-1975 (Box 78)
      - 1982 (Box 79)
    - University Heritage Committee (Box 79)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 79)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 79)
      - 1978-1982 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 79)
      - 1982, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 79)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 79)
      - 1986 (Box 79)
      - 1987 (Box 79)
    - Hine, Maynard - Committee to Plan an Affair to Honor, 1973 (Box 79)
    - Historic Preservation Committee (Box 79)
      - 1979-1996 (Box 79)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 79)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 79)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 79)
      - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978, (2 folder) (Box 79)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 79)
    - Honeywell House Program Committee (Box 79)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee (RESTRICTED) (Box 79)
      - 1971-1976 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 79)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 79)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 79)
      - 1985 (Box 79)
      - 1986 (Box 79)
    - University Honors Committee (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 79)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 79)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
    - Hoosier Heritage Hall Committee (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 79)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 79)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 79)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 79)
      - 1981 (Box 79)
    - Indiana Bell Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 79)
    - Indiana Daily Student Publications Committee (Box 79)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 79)
      - 1983 (Box 79)
    - Indiana Medical Education Foundation Trust Committee (Box 79)
      - 1969-1971 (Box 79)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 79)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 79)
    - IU Press committee (Box 79)
      - 1983 (Box 79)
      - 1986 (Box 79)
    - IUPUI Committee on Goals and Objectives (Box 79)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 79)
    - Insurance Retirement Systems Committee (Box 79)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 79)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
    - Internal Affairs Committee (Box 79)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
    - International Exchange of Persons Committee (Box 79)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
    - International Memberships Committee, 1981 (Box 79)
    - Investment Committee, 1986 (Box 79)
    - Irwin Committees, 1981-1982 (Box 79)
    - David Starr Jordan (Box 79)
      - Award Committee, 1986 (Box 79)
      - Prize Award, 1987 (Box 79)
      - Award Committee, 1987 (Box 79)
      - Centennial Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 79)
    - Jordan Hall (including Lieber Room), 1971-1982 (Box 79)
    - Jordan Hall Rededication Committee, 1984; (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - College Journal Circulation Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 79)
    - Labor Advisory Board (Box 79)
      - General, 1977-1979 (Box 79)
      - Committee (Box 79)
        - 1975-1977 (Box 79)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 79)
        - 1985 (Box 79)
    - Advisory Committee on Labor Education (Box 79)
      - General (Box 79)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 79)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 79)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 79)
        - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 80)
        - 1979-1980 (Box 80)
      - Statewide, 1986 (Box 80)
    - Latin American Fellowships and Scholarships Committee, 1984 (Box 80)
    - Legionnaires Disease Ad Hoc Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 80)
    - Committee Letters (Box 80)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
    - Library Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 80)
    - Library Committee (Box 80)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
    - Library Personnel (Committee on the Career Status of), 1972 (Box 80)
    - Leibenow Committees (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973 (Box 80)
    - Lifelong Learning (Committee on), 1977 (Box 80)
    - Lilly Library Visiting Committee (Box 80)
      - 1979 (Box 80)
      - 1986 (Box 80)
    - Little 500/ Soccer Facility Dedication, 1983 (Box 80)
    - Lombardi Appointed Committees (Box 80)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 80)
      - 1983 (Box 80)
    - Long Range Planning Committee (Box 80)
      - 1972 (Box 80)
      - 1981-1982, (2 folders) (Box 80)
    - Management Information Steering Committee (Box 80)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 80)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 80)
    - Management Information System Cost Benefit Review Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
    - Mathers Museum (Box 80)
      - Dedication Committee, 1982 (Box 80)
      - General, 1984 (Box 80)
    - Dean Merritt Appointed Committees, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
    - Mulholland Appointed Committees, 1980-1981 (Box 80)
    - Names of Current Committee Chairmen, 1973 (Box 80)
    - All University Committee on Names (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 80)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 80)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 80)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 80)
      - 1984 (Box 80)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 80)
      - 1986 (Box 80)
      - 1987 (Box 80)
    - Natural Areas Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
    - Necrology Committee (Box 80)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 80)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 80)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 80)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 80)
    - O'Brien Lecture Series Committee (Box 80)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 80)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 80)
    - Occupational Education Programs Committee (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 80)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 80)
      - President's, 1973-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 80)
      - 1985 (Box 80)
    - Operations Advisory Committee (Box 80)
      - 1971-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1974-1979 (Box 80)
    - Overseas Study Committee (Box 80)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 80)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 80)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 80)
      - 1984 (Box 80)
    - Owen-Wylie Halls Centenary Committee, 1985 (Box 80)
    - Parking Study Committee (Box 80)
      - General, 1971-1972 (Box 80)
      - Inner campus (Box 80)
        - 1983 (Box 80)
        - 1984 (Box 80)
    - Pinnell/Faris Appointed Committees, 1980-1982 (Box 80)
    - Policy Review Committee, 1976 (Box 81)
    - Power Plant Review Committee, 1985 (Box 81)
    - Presidential Evaluation Committee (Box 81)
      - 1973, (2 folders) (Box 81)
      - 1974-1979 (Box 81)
      - 1979, (2 folders) (Box 81)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1986 (Box 81)
    - President's Advisory Committees, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box 81)
    - President's Advisory Committee on Matters Relating to Education (Box 81)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 81)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 81)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 81)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 81)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 81)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 81)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 81)
    - President's Advisory Committee on General Matters Regarding Teacher Education (Box 81)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 81)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 81)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 81)
    - President's Advisory Committee on the Selection of a Vice President for Development, 1975 (Box 81)
    - President's Policy Committee (Box 81)
      - 1971-1974 (Box 81)
      - 1975 (Box 81)
    - Printing and Duplicating Equipment Committee, 1971 (Box 81)
    - Professional Building Construction Committee- Frank McKinney, 1971-1972 (Box 81)
    - Professional Staff Representation Committee, 1984 (Box 81)
    - Proffitt Plaque Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 81)
    - Promotions Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 81)
    - School of Public and Environmental Affairs Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 81)
    - Public Performance Policies Committee (Box 81)
      - 1971 (Box 81)
      - 1971 (Box 81)
    - Publications Committee (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 82)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 82)
    - Radiation Safety Committee, 1970 (Box 82)
    - Research Center for Language Science Visiting Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 82)
    - University Research Committee (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 82)
    - Residential and Graduate Division Advisory Committee (Box 82)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 82)
      - 1986 (Box 82)
    - University Residential Policy Committee, 1986 (Box 82)
    - University Research Operations Committee (Box 82)
      - 1979-1980, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 82)
      - 1984 (Box 82)
      - 1985 (Box 82)
    - University Research Policy Committee, 1981 (Box 82)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC) (Box 82)
      - General, 1982 (Box 82)
      - Affairs Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 82)
      - Program Desirability Committee, 1981 (Box 82)
    - Residence Life Review Committee (Box 82)
      - 1986 (Box 82)
      - 1987 (Box 82)
    - Standing Committee on Residence (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 82)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 82)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 82)
      - 1984 (Box 82)
    - Residence Life Review Committee, 1984 (Box 82)
    - Residency Committee, 1986 (Box 82)
    - Retention Task Force, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Retirement Housing Committee, 1974 (Box 82)
    - Committee on Administration and Departmental Reviews (Box 82)
      - 1979 (Box 82)
      - 1980 (Box 82)
      - Reports, 1980 (Box 82)
      - 1981-1987, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1981 (Box 82)
      - 1982, (2 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1983 (Box 82)
      - 1984 (Box 82)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 82)
      - Review from Dean K Gene Faris, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Departmental Reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 82)
    - Review Committees (Box 82)
      - Giust, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
      - Glenn A. Goerke, 1985 (Box 82)
      - Graduate Services, 1983 (Box 82)
      - Gros Louis, 1984 (Box 82)
      - Glenn W. Irwin, 1979 (Box 82)
      - Lomabardi, 1984 (Box 82)
      - Committee Lombardi, John Dean for international programs, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
      - Orescanin, 1981 (Box 82)
      - W. George Pinnell, 1979 (Box 82)
      - Rhodes- Marshall Scholarsip, 1971 (Box 82)
      - Thomson, 1984 (Box 82)
      - Williams, 1980 (Box 82)
      - Wolfson, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Recognition Committee for Claude Rich, 1975 (Box 82)
    - Addision Locke Roache Memorial Fund Committee (Box 82)
      - 1976-1978 (Box 82)
      - 1979 (Box 82)
      - 1981-1985 (Box 82)
      - 1982 (Box 82)
      - 1984 (Box 82)
    - Salary Administration Review Committee, 1975 (Box 82)
    - Salary Structure Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
    - U.S. Savings bonds Committee, 1985 (Box 82)
    - Committee on Scholarships and Financial Aid (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 82)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82)
      - 1980-1983 (Box 82)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 82)
    - Science Advisory Committee (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 82)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 82)
    - Search and Screen Committees (Box 82)
      - 1982 (Box 82)
      - Memberships, 1984 (Box 82)
      - Alumni, 1986 (Box 82)
      - Athletic, 1978 (Box 82)
      - For IUPUI Chancellor, 1975 (Box 82)
      - Final Report of, for Chancellor for IUPUI, 1973 (Box 82)
      - International Programs Dean, 1986 (Box 82)
      - To Select Dean of School of business, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - For Dean of Division of General and Technical Studies, 1974 (Box 82)
      - For Associate Dean of Arts and Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - For Chancellor for IU East, 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - For Dean of College of Education, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - Committee Appointed by Byrum Carter, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - Search and Screen Committee for Dean of Law School (Box 82)
        - 1973-1976 (Box 82)
        - 1984 (Box 82)
        - 1986 (Box 82)
        - 1987 (Box 82)
      - For Director of libraries, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - Final Summary IU School of Medicine Dean Search and Screen committee, 1974 (Box 82)
      - Dean of School of Medicine IUPUI, 1974 (Box 82)
      - Director of Indiana Memorial Union, undated (Box 82)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 82)
      - Vice president Bloomington, 1979-1980 (Box 82)
      - Chancellor Kokomo campus, undated (Box 82)
      - IU Northwest, undated (Box 82)
      - Dr. Peggy Elliott, undated (Box 82)
      - Dr. Anthony Catanese, undated (Box 82)
      - Dr. Janet Travis, undated (Box 82)
      - Chancelor IU Northwest, 1984 (Box 82)
      - IUPUI, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
      - Associate Dean of Indianapolis, 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - South Bend Chancellor, 1987 (Box 82)
      - Dean for Research and Graduate development, 1976-1977 (Box 82)
    - Committee to Study the Role of Division of Social Service, 1965 (Box 82)
    - Space Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
    - State Fair Committee, 1987 (Box 82)
    - Statewide Planning Committee on Athletics (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
    - Student Affairs Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
    - Student Conduct Code Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 82)
    - Student Health Service Advisory Committee (Box 82)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 82)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 82)
    - Student Health Insurance Committee (Box 82)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 82)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 82)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 82)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 82)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 82)
    - Student Health Services Policy Committee, 1986 (Box 82)
    - Student Records Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
    - Student Records, Committee to Review the Policies and Procedures, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
    - Student Recruitment Procedures and Policies Committee (Box 82)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 82)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 82)
    - Student Representation Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 82)
    - Taskforce on Student Rights and Responsibilities (Box 82)
      - 1985 (Box 82)
      - 1986 (Box 82)
      - 1987 (Box 82)
    - Summer Session Review Committee (Box 82)
      - 1984 (Box 82)
      - Responses, 1984 (Box 83)
      - Back-up material, 1984 (Box 83)
    - Teacher Education Committee (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 83)
    - TIAA/CREF, Committee to Handle Exceptions to our Present Policies for Admission (Box 83)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 83)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 83)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 83)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 83)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 83)
    - Track Site Committee, 1974 (Box 83)
    - Transition Committee, 1987 (Box 83)
    - University Press Faculty Committee (Box 83)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 83)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 83)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 83)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 83)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 83)
    - University Press Monograph Committee (Box 83)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
    - University Grand Marshal, 1975 (Box 83)
    - University Research Committee (Box 83)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 83)
      - Agenda, 1971 (Box 83)
    - University Research and Development Committee (Box 83)
      - 1971 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
    - University Research Operations Committee (Box 83)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 83)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 83)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 83)
    - Urban Affairs Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 83)
    - Urban Universities Committee (Box 83)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 83)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 83)
    - Vocational Education Committee (Box 83)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 83)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 83)
      - 1975-1976, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 83)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 83)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 83)
    - Wage-Price Freeze (Box 83)
      - Review Committee for System Services, 1971 (Box 83)
      - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee, 1971 (Box 83)
    - Wells Recognition Award Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 83)
    - Widman, John - Committee to Draft a Memorial Tribute, 1972 (Box 83)
    - Williams Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 83)
    - Wolf Trap (Indiana Committee on), 1980 (Box 83)
    - Woodburn Guild Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 83)
    - Women's Advisory Committees (Box 83)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 83)
    - Committee on the Status of Women, 1972-1973 (Box 83)
    - X-ray Committee, 1973 (Box 83)
    - Committees (Outside IU) (Box 83)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
      - 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 83)
      - State University Computer Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 83)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 83)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 83)
      - 1984 (Box 83)
  - Common Fund, 1972 (Box 83)
  - Communication Services Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 83)
  - Community Colleges (Box 83)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 83)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 83)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 83)
  - Community Resources Workshop Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 83)
  - Comparative Literature (Box 83)
    - 1973 (Box 83)
    - Grievances, 1985-1987 (Box 83)
  - Computer Literacy, 1982-1983 (Box 84)